Kim Possible is a family, action, adventure film directed by Adam B. Stein.
Everyday teen hero Kim Possible and her best friend Ron Stoppable embark on their
freshman year of high school, all while saving the world from evil villains.
While Kim and Ron have always been one step ahead of their opponents, navigating the social
hierarchy of high school is more challenging than the action-hero ever imagined.
With Drakken and Shego lurking in the wings, Kim must rely on her family and Team
Possible—Ron, tech-genius Wade, new friend Athena, and Rufus, a Naked mole-rat.
Kim Possible, played by Sadie Stanley.
Ron Stoppable, played by Sean Giambrone.
Athena, played by Ciara Riley Wilson.
Shego, played by Taylor Ortega.
Nana Possible, played by Connie Ray.
Wade, played by Issac Ryan Brown.
Kim Possible is a 2019 American action comedy television film that premiered as a
Disney Channel Original Movie on Disney Channel on February 15, 2019.
Loosely based on the 2002–2007 animated series of the same name created by Mark McCorkle and Bob
Schooley, the film stars Sadie Stanley, Sean Giambrone, and Ciara Riley Wilson.
The film explores themes of spy, genius, teenage girl, heroine, spy spoof.
The tone is lighthearted.